question_data = [
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Axolotl is an amphibian that can spend its whole life in a larval state.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Greenland is almost as big as Africa.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that "
                 "was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In Scandinavian languages, the letter &Aring; means river.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "It&#039;s not possible to format a write-protected DVD-R Hard Disk.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "One of Barack Obama's United States presidential campaign "
                 "slogan's was 'Yes We Can'.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing 'Spoons'; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
